

Yu-Lien 沈佑璉 (UX Reaserch, UI Design, VR Design)

Hi, I'm Vicky. A passionate designer with experience in UIUX and VR design, I thrive in collaborating with interdisciplinary teams and using design thinking to enhance user experiences.

Email: yulien860108@gmail.com

Phone: +886 937 241 621



Education

2021/08-2024/01

National Cheng Kung University

Industrial Design - Master GPA: 3.94

2015/08-2019/09

Asia University

Creative Product Design -**Bachelor**



Skills

Design

VR Design, User Research, Interface Design, APP Design, Visual Design, **Product Design**

Tools

Unity 3D, Figma, Adobe XD, Photoshop, Illustrator, Premiere, In Design, iClone, Blender, Alias



Thesis

Title:

Virtual Reality Based with Hand Tracking Technology for Neurological **Examination Training** System Design



🐴 語言

English (Advanced) TOEFL iBT 96



Experience

2023/07-2024/01

VR Project - Neurological Examination Training System

Identify needs and pain points from the stakeholders, and carry out overall planning for the VR system, including interface design, and interaction design. Using User Journey Map, Storyboard and Flow Chart to communicate and collaborate with physicians and engineers. Finally, produce a prototype and gather user feedback of using the system.

2022/07-2023/08

VR Project - Project Assistant - NIHSS Training System

Primarily responsible for design of the turorial segment of the system. Ultimately, produce the VR system and conduct usability testing and validation.

Awarded Silver Prize in the Ministry of Education's 2022 Forward-looking Special Topic **Implementation Competition** for the Innovation in Application of Technology (AR/ VR/MR/XR).

2022/03-2022/06

App Design - Financial Management App

Identify the target user and their needs and pain points, plan the usage flow, create a Function Map, and communicate with engineers. Proceed with interface design and prototype development.

2022/02-2022/06

UI/UX Design - Industry-Academia Collaboration for Uniring Cleaning Robot

Competitive analysis and product positioning for new models, and plan humanmachine interaction scenarios. Develop operation flow and wireframes.

2021/07-2022/05

VR Project - Virtual Curation Exhibition System

CIS design, system planning, product positioning, and business model development. Second place in the Ministry of Economic Affairs' 2021 Communication Contest 5G **Leading Innovation Application** Competition in the Digital Entertainment category.